[{"answer": "Well, you can.", "docId": "110308pmt", "aSentId": 20, "question": "When you see what's going on, not just in Libya now but also in the Middle East, do you quite believe it?", "qSentId": 19}, {"answer": "I don't know that I would lump Mubarak with Saddam Hussein or Gadhafi.", "docId": "110308pmt", "aSentId": 34, "question": "What should an American be thinking right now about these characters?", "qSentId": 33}, {"answer": "Yes, indeed.", "docId": "110308pmt", "aSentId": 38, "question": "Much different?", "qSentId": 37}, {"answer": "No, not at all.", "docId": "110308pmt", "aSentId": 51, "question": "When you see this, do you feel uncomfortable when you watch it?", "qSentId": 50}, {"answer": "I think quite the contrary with Iraq.", "docId": "110308pmt", "aSentId": 66, "question": "-- Tunisia, Egypt, Libya, do you not wish you'd waited perhaps?", "qSentId": 65}, {"answer": "There is an argument, and I have heard this espoused by family members of mine, who've served with the British military in Iraq and Afghanistan.", "docId": "110308pmt", "aSentId": 76, "question": "Who knows what's going to happen in Egypt?", "qSentId": 75}, {"answer": "Well, there -- sure, there's a free press.", "docId": "110308pmt", "aSentId": 85, "question": "Are they getting it?", "qSentId": 84}, {"answer": "Well, I guess you feel both.", "docId": "110308pmt", "aSentId": 129, "question": "When you see Gadhafi going, when you see potentially the House of Sal being threatened, when you see this complete transformation in the Middle East, do you feel excited or do you feel very apprehensive about what might happen, for instance, to Israel in all this?", "qSentId": 128}, {"answer": "Oh, my goodness, yes.", "docId": "110308pmt", "aSentId": 141, "question": "And that would be a threat to the United States, wouldn't it, if that happened?", "qSentId": 140}, {"answer": "No, I wouldn't.", "docId": "110308pmt", "aSentId": 143, "question": "So if you take that as a potential scenario, if you were now in the administration, and was still defense secretary, would you be considering now an invasion of Libya because that would be the way to stop potentially what happened in Iran happening in Libya?", "qSentId": 142}, {"answer": "Because there was broad, uniform, almost un-debatable agreement that there was a risk of stockpiles of weapons of mass destruction in the case of Iraq.", "docId": "110308pmt", "aSentId": 153, "question": "Why are the people of Libya being left to die?", "qSentId": 152}, {"answer": "No, it's not.", "docId": "110308pmt", "aSentId": 156, "question": "Well, isn't that slightly disingenuous?", "qSentId": 155}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110308pmt", "aSentId": 181, "question": "In Iraq?", "qSentId": 180}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110308pmt", "aSentId": 191, "question": "So if that is the yardstick for why Iraq happened, would you have been very happy to have gone in regardless of the WMD issue?", "qSentId": 190}, {"answer": "Of course you have regrets.", "docId": "110308pmt", "aSentId": 205, "question": "Did you have any regrets?", "qSentId": 204}, {"answer": "Oh, my goodness.", "docId": "110308pmt", "aSentId": 236, "question": "Have there been times during that period when you've shed tears over American troops?", "qSentId": 235}, {"answer": "I was in my office, having breakfast next door with a group of congressmen when the plane hit the World Trade Center tower, the first one.", "docId": "110308pmt", "aSentId": 257, "question": "Where were you the moment you heard?", "qSentId": 256}, {"answer": "Accident.", "docId": "110308pmt", "aSentId": 261, "question": "And was what your first thought when the second plane hit?", "qSentId": 260}, {"answer": "I didn't have a gut feeling.", "docId": "110308pmt", "aSentId": 266, "question": "And who did you -- who did your gut tell you may be responsible?", "qSentId": 265}, {"answer": "Well -- yes, indeed.", "docId": "110308pmt", "aSentId": 272, "question": "And these were people that you've worked with, that you knew personally?", "qSentId": 271}, {"answer": "I think when something happens like that, there's a period where you have to sort it out.", "docId": "110308pmt", "aSentId": 290, "question": "Is it always going to be confused in a situation like that?", "qSentId": 289}, {"answer": "Well, let me respond.", "docId": "110308pmt", "aSentId": 307, "question": "Didn't you have to do that for the soul of your country?", "qSentId": 306}, {"answer": "I have -- to go back just one second.", "docId": "110308pmt", "aSentId": 331, "question": "Why are we going after the guy who didn't appear to have anything to do with 9/11?", "qSentId": 330}, {"answer": "I have no idea.", "docId": "110308pmt", "aSentId": 342, "question": "Would America have gone to war with Saddam without 9/11?", "qSentId": 341}, {"answer": "It depends on all of those risk factors.", "docId": "110308pmt", "aSentId": 344, "question": "Would you like it to have done it?", "qSentId": 343}, {"answer": "He's the one who makes decisions.", "docId": "110308pmt", "aSentId": 352, "question": "Wouldn't your answer be an unequivocal of course it was?", "qSentId": 351}, {"answer": "No, it isn't.", "docId": "110308pmt", "aSentId": 354, "question": "But that's a copout, isn't it?", "qSentId": 353}, {"answer": "I think that's probably right.", "docId": "110308pmt", "aSentId": 385, "question": "If you'd been president you would have taken that decision?", "qSentId": 384}, {"answer": "I think so.", "docId": "110308pmt", "aSentId": 400, "question": "Was it a mistake to label this a war on terror?", "qSentId": 399}, {"answer": "I did.", "docId": "110308pmt", "aSentId": 413, "question": "Did you argue again it at the time?", "qSentId": 412}, {"answer": "Well, I wasn't overruled, there was a discussion, and people had different views --", "docId": "110308pmt", "aSentId": 416, "question": "Why were you overruled?", "qSentId": 415}, {"answer": "Well, I don't know - I had several problems with the phrase.", "docId": "110308pmt", "aSentId": 421, "question": "I know, but why did he overrule you?", "qSentId": 420}, {"answer": "Exactly.", "docId": "110308pmt", "aSentId": 429, "question": "It's really a counterterrorism operation, isn't it?", "qSentId": 428}, {"answer": "I think that the word war is imperfect because it leaves people with the impression of World War I, World War II, it begins, it ends.", "docId": "110308pmt", "aSentId": 431, "question": "It's no longer a war, is it?", "qSentId": 430}, {"answer": "You bet.", "docId": "110308pmt", "aSentId": 435, "question": "Is America safer today, do you think?", "qSentId": 434}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110308pmt", "aSentId": 474, "question": "ORGAN: Isn't it extraordinary that the world's greatest military force can't find a guy on a horse?", "qSentId": 473}, {"answer": "I do.", "docId": "110308pmt", "aSentId": 483, "question": "You think he still alive?", "qSentId": 482}, {"answer": "No, it's not.", "docId": "110308pmt", "aSentId": 498, "question": "That's the same thing, isn't it?", "qSentId": 497}, {"answer": "They're tough decisions, you bet.", "docId": "110308pmt", "aSentId": 513, "question": "The decisions that you took collectively?", "qSentId": 512}, {"answer": "I don't think there has been.", "docId": "110308pmt", "aSentId": 515, "question": "Because they were so polarizing these decisions, that inevitably there's been an extended blame game ever since?", "qSentId": 514}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110308pmt", "aSentId": 517, "question": "But there has, hasn't there?", "qSentId": 516}, {"answer": "Not too much, no.", "docId": "110308pmt", "aSentId": 519, "question": "You don't think so?", "qSentId": 518}, {"answer": "You're in public life a heck of a long time before Iraq came along, for example.", "docId": "110308pmt", "aSentId": 521, "question": "Compared to other administrations?", "qSentId": 520}, {"answer": "No, sorry about the decision making that led to it.", "docId": "110308pmt", "aSentId": 546, "question": "You mean sorry about the loss of life?", "qSentId": 545}, {"answer": "You could.", "docId": "110308pmt", "aSentId": 557, "question": "If you submit your resignation and he doesn't accept it, can't you just resign anyway?", "qSentId": 556}, {"answer": "I think in retrospect at the time, I felt very reluctant to walk -- our country was in a war, to walk away from it when the president tells you he doesn't want you to, is a hard thing to do.", "docId": "110308pmt", "aSentId": 559, "question": "Do you wish you had?", "qSentId": 558}, {"answer": "Here tonight, the latest from Libya, Gadhafi's forces seem to be gaining the upper hand at least in the battle for the city of Zawiya, poorly armed opposition forces and civilians under fire in that surrounded city.", "docId": "110308pmt", "aSentId": 571, "question": "My colleague, Anderson Cooper, Anderson, what have you got on your show tonight?", "qSentId": 570}, {"answer": "Yes, of course.", "docId": "110308pmt", "aSentId": 596, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 595}, {"answer": "It's still in the State Department.", "docId": "110308pmt", "aSentId": 599, "question": "And you did say you just stand up?", "qSentId": 598}, {"answer": "I do.", "docId": "110308pmt", "aSentId": 603, "question": "You still do that?", "qSentId": 602}, {"answer": "It's just weird.", "docId": "110308pmt", "aSentId": 605, "question": "Why do you act like that's odd?", "qSentId": 604}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110308pmt", "aSentId": 614, "question": "Didn't it dawn on you to take a rest?", "qSentId": 613}, {"answer": "You get up earlier than Condoleezza Rice.", "docId": "110308pmt", "aSentId": 616, "question": "Why would one want to do that?", "qSentId": 615}, {"answer": "No, it's not proper at 78.", "docId": "110308pmt", "aSentId": 624, "question": "And you do a proper workout?", "qSentId": 623}, {"answer": "Goodness.", "docId": "110308pmt", "aSentId": 628, "question": "What's been the human toll on you, do you think, from all that time you had in office, particularly through the very difficult years of the early part of the century?", "qSentId": 627}, {"answer": "Of course, it's true.", "docId": "110308pmt", "aSentId": 636, "question": "On 9/11, you didn't call your wife?", "qSentId": 635}, {"answer": "Well, I was busy, goodness gracious.", "docId": "110308pmt", "aSentId": 643, "question": "Why didn't you?", "qSentId": 642}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110308pmt", "aSentId": 651, "question": "Would you describe her as long suffering?", "qSentId": 650}, {"answer": "Well, of course -", "docId": "110308pmt", "aSentId": 655, "question": "What was it like for you, trying to juggle the two things?", "qSentId": 654}, {"answer": "Drug addiction is such a terrible, terribly difficult thing and it's heartbreaking to see a human being you love go down and down and down.", "docId": "110308pmt", "aSentId": 657, "question": "Drug prioritized?", "qSentId": 656}, {"answer": "Yes, sure.", "docId": "110308pmt", "aSentId": 663, "question": "Did you think you had lost him?", "qSentId": 662}, {"answer": "Well, I guess the only thing you can say is hope.", "docId": "110308pmt", "aSentId": 667, "question": "When you see what's happening with Charlie Sheen and you obviously -- Martin Sheen his father feels helpless about the situation, is there any advice you can give someone when a son just won't listen?", "qSentId": 666}, {"answer": "They do.", "docId": "110308pmt", "aSentId": 677, "question": "All the profits go to military charities, is that right?", "qSentId": 676}, {"answer": "No, no.", "docId": "110308pmt", "aSentId": 683, "question": "But was he right?", "qSentId": 682}, {"answer": "I had respect for most of the people that I've worked with.", "docId": "110308pmt", "aSentId": 688, "question": "You've served under four presidents, who are your political heroes?", "qSentId": 687}, {"answer": "Each one was different.", "docId": "110308pmt", "aSentId": 691, "question": "People you thought were genuinely politically heroic?", "qSentId": 690}, {"answer": "I'm neither.", "docId": "110308pmt", "aSentId": 700, "question": "If you were to summarize yourself, would you say you're a dove or a hawk?", "qSentId": 699}, {"answer": "He served.", "docId": "110308pmt", "aSentId": 705, "question": "You can write it right now on a tombstone?", "qSentId": 704}, {"answer": "I think so.", "docId": "110308pmt", "aSentId": 707, "question": "Just that?", "qSentId": 706}]